A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Subject File, 1951-1981; 4; 85 Cubic Feet 170 boxes: 164 legal document boxes, 4 record cartons, 2 half-legal document box.
    - Taylor-Berelson Program (Maternal and Child Health Program) (MCH), 1970-1975; 13
      - Egypt- Maps, 1971 (Box 603, Folder 5850)
      - Egypt - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 603, Folder 5851)
      - El Salvador, 1975 (Box 603, Folder 5852)
      - Ethiopia, 1971-1973 (Box 603, Folder 5853)
      - Fiji, 1972 (Box 603, Folder 5854)
      - Gambia, 1971-1973 (Box 603, Folder 5855)
      - Ghana, 1971-1974 (Box 604, Folder 5856)
      - Guatemala, undated (Box 604, Folder 5857)
      - Haiti, 1969-1974 (Box 604, Folder 5858-5859)
      - India, 1971-1974 (Box 604, Folder 5860)
      - Iran, 1967-1974 (Box 604, Folder 5861)
      - Iraq, 1972 (Box 604, Folder 5862)
      - Jamaica, 1971-1972 (Box 604, Folder 5863)
      - Kenya, 1971-1972 (Box 604, Folder 5864)
      - Korea, 1971-1974 (Box 604, Folder 5865)
      - Malaysia, 1971-1972 (Box 604, Folder 5866)
      - Mexico - Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 605, Folder 5867)
      - Mexico - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 605, Folder 5868)
      - Mexico - Reports and Trips, 1973-1974 (Box 605, Folder 5869)
      - Mexico - Vital Documents, 1970-1971 (Box 605, Folder 5870)
      - Mexico - Meetings, 1973 (Box 605, Folder 5871)
      - Mexico - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 605, Folder 5872)
      - Morocco, 1972 (Box 605, Folder 5873)
      - New Guinea, 1973 (Box 605, Folder 5874)
      - Niger - Africare, 1971-1972 (Box 605, Folder 5875)
      - Senegal, 1968-1971 (Box 605, Folder 5876)
      - Taiwan, 1971-1974 (Box 605, Folder 5877)
      - Tanzania, 1972 (Box 605, Folder 5878)
      - Thailand - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 606, Folder 5879)
      - Thailand - Reports and Trips, 1971-1975 (Box 606, Folder 5880)
      - Thailand - Vital Documents, 1971-1973 (Box 606, Folder 5881-5882)
      - Tunisia, 1970-1975 (Box 606, Folder 5883-5884)
      - Uganda, undated (Box 606, Folder 5885)
      - United States, 1972-1973 (Box 606, Folder 5886)
      - Zaire, 1972 (Box 606, Folder 5887)
      - Zambia, 1972 (Box 606, Folder 5888)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Country Reports, 1971 (Box 599, Folder 5797-5801)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Summary Data Sheets, undated (Box 600, Folder 5802)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Directory - African Demographers, 1967-1970 (Box 600, Folder 5803)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Data on Demographic Training, undated (Box 600, Folder 5804)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Demographic Training (Asia) - Reports, Correspondence, Data, undated (Box 600, Folder 5805-5806)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Tropical Africa - Second Mapping Report, undated (Box 600, Folder 5807)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Map AF Report - North Africa and Middle East, undated (Box 600, Folder 5808)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Map - Latin America, 1971 (Box 600, Folder 5809)
    - Training in Demography and Family Planning (Population Council Survey) - Inter-regional Seminar on Demographic Aspects of Manpower, Moscow, Activities, and Trips, 1970 (Box 600, Folder 5810)
    - Women - Fertility, 1970-1971 (Box 601, Folder 5811)
    - Women - Menstruation, 1971 (Box 601, Folder 5812)
    - Women - Sociology of, 1970-1971 (Box 601, Folder 5813)
    - World Bank Survey, 1970-1971 (Box 601, Folder 5814)
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer), 1971-1974 (Box 601, Folder 5815)
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer) - Current Developments, 1973 (Box 607, Folder 5889)
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer) - Publication Manager, undated (Box 607, Folder 5890)
      Restricted from research - contains personnel information.
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer) - Technical Advisory Committee (TAC) Meetings, May 1973-1974 (Box 607, Folder 5891-5895)
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer) - Technical Advisory Committee (TAC) Meetings, July 1972-May 1973 (Box 608, Folder 5896-5901)
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer) - Technical Advisory Committee (TAC) Meetings, 1972 (Box 609, Folder 5902-5903)
    - World Fertility Survey (Seltzer) - Technical Advisory Committee (TAC) - Initial Period, 1972 (Box 609, Folder 5904)
    - World Population Year, 1974 (Box 601, Folder 5816)
    - Family Planning Newsletter, S. M. Keeny, Volume 1-4, 1963-1974 (Box 610, Folder 1)
    - Vivian B. Allen Foundation Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 610, Folder 2-3)
    - Organization and Storage Files, 1974-1976 (Box 610, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd Death - Condolence Letters, 1978 (Box 610, Folder 5)
    - AID Progress Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 611, Folder 1-3)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs (Box 611, Folder 4-5)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs (Box 612, Folder 1-2)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Newman, Jeanne (Box 612, Folder 3)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Fawcett, James T. (Box 612, Folder 4)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Huey, Harris (Box 612, Folder 5)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Satterthwaite, Adaline P. (Box 612, Folder 6)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Jones, Gavin W. (Box 612, Folder 7)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Taylor, Howard C., Jr. (Box 612, Folder 8)
    - Office of Communications - Former Staff Photographs - Keeny, S. M. (Box 612, Folder 9)
    - United Nations - General, 1982 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    - United Nations - NGO - General, 1981-1982 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    - United Nations - NGO - CSDHA, 1981 (Box 613, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - NGO - ECOSOC - Congo, 1972-1982 (Box 613, Folder 4)
    - United Nations - NGO - FAO, 1977-1981 (Box 613, Folder 5)
    - United Nations - NGO - ILO, 1978-1982 (Box 613, Folder 6)
    - United Nations - Population Division, 1972-1979 (Box 613, Folder 7)
    - United Nations - NGO - UNDP, 1978-1979 (Box 613, Folder 8)
    - United Nations - NGO - UNFPA, 1978-1982 (Box 613, Folder 9)
    - United Nations - NGO - UNICEF, 1971-1982 (Box 613, Folder 10)
    - United Nations - Women's Programs, 1980 (Box 613, Folder 11)
    - United Nations - NGO - WHO, 1975-1980 (Box 614, Folder 1)
    - United Nations - General, 1983-1985 (Box 614, Folder 2)
    - United Nations - NGO - General, 1983-1985 (Box 614, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - NGO - ECOSOC - Congo, 1983-1985 (Box 614, Folder 4)
    - United Nations - NGO - FAO, 1982-1985 (Box 614, Folder 5)
    - United Nations - NGO - ILO, 1983-1985 (Box 614, Folder 6)
    - United Nations - Population Division, 1980-1985 (Box 614, Folder 7)
    - United Nations - NGO - UNDP, 1980-1985 (Box 614, Folder 8)
    - United Nations - NGO - UNFPA, 1980-1985 (Box 614, Folder 9)
    - United Nations - NGO - UNICEF, 1983-1985 (Box 614, Folder 10)
    - Permission to Reprint from PC (Publications), 1972-1976 (Box 615, Folder 1-4)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) - Production - PDR 3, No 1 and 2 (Box 615, Folder 5)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 1, Issue 1 through PDR Volume 3, Issue 4, 1975-1978 (Box 616, Folder 1-45)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 2, Issue 1 through PDR Volume 2, Issue 4 (Box 617, Folder 24-50)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 4, Issue 1 and 2 (Box 617, Folder 1-23)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 4, Issue 3, 1978 (Box 618, Folder 1-14)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 4, Issue 4, 1978 (Box 619, Folder 1-10)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 5, Issue 1, 1978 (Box 620, Folder 1-12)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 5, Issue 2, 1979 (Box 621, Folder 1-9)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 5, Issue 3, 1979 (Box 621, Folder 10-13)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 5, Issue 3, 1979 (Box 622, Folder 1-8)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 5, Issue 4, 1979-1980 (Box 622, Folder 9-11)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 5, Issue 4, 1979-1980 (Box 623, Folder 1-6)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 7, Issue 1, 1981 (Box 634, Folder 1-10)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 7, Issue 2, 1981 (Box 634, Folder 11-17)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 7, Issue 2, 1981 (Box 635, Folder 1-3)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 7, Issue 3, 1981 (Box 635, Folder 4-13)
    - Population and Development Review (PDR) Files - PDR Volume 7, Issue 4, 1981 (Box 636, Folder 1-10)
    - Permission to Reprint, 1977-1979 (Box 623, Folder 7-9)
    - Budget 1975 (Box 624, Folder 1)
    - Technical Assistance Division (TAD) - IUD, 1970-1976 (Box 624, Folder 2)
    - Budget 1976, 1975-1977 (Box 624, Folder 3-4)
    - Moss - 25-Year Chronicle, 1952-1977, 1978 (Box 625, Folder 1-3)
    - Key People Program, 1968-1975 (Box 625, Folder 4)
    - Key People Program, 1968-1975 (Box 626, Folder 1-2)
    - Mexico - Country File, 1969-1977 (Box 626, Folder 3)
    - Brazil - Country File, 1969-1978 (Box 626, Folder 4)
    - Population Council 1977 Program Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 626, Folder 5)
    - Population Council 1978 Program Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Population Council 1979 Program Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 627, Folder 2)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Correspondence and General Material, 1976-1980 (Box 627, Folder 3)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Board of Trustees - 1981 (Box 627, Folder 4)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Correspondence and General Material - 1981 (Box 627, Folder 5)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Board of Trustees - 1982 (Box 627, Folder 6)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Correspondence and General Material - 1982 (Box 627, Folder 7)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Finance Committee - 1983 (Box 627, Folder 8)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Board of Trustees - 1983 (Box 627, Folder 9)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Correspondence and General Material - 1983 (Box 628, Folder 1)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Correspondence and General Material - 1984 (Box 628, Folder 2)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Board of Trustees - 1984 (Box 628, Folder 3)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Executive Committee - 1984 (Box 628, Folder 4)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Finance Committee - 1984 (Box 628, Folder 5)
    - Real Estate, 1983 (Box 628, Folder 6)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Correspondence and General Material - 1985 (Box 628, Folder 7)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Board of Trustees - 1985 (Box 629, Folder 1)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Executive Committee - 1985 (Box 629, Folder 2)
    - Experiment in International Living (EIL) - Finance Committee - 1985 (Box 629, Folder 3)
    - Program Analysis Data - Multiple Correlation - India (Box 630)
    - Program Analysis Data - National Programs Project - India, Principal Component Analysis, 1973-1974 (Box 630)
    - Program Analysis Data - Chapter 1 - 75 Countries (Box 631)
    - Program Analysis Data - Chapter 4 - States of India, Profiles (Box 631)
    - Program Analysis Data - Chapter 3 - East and Southeast Asia, Profiles; East and Southeast Asia, Comparative Analysis (Box 631)
    - Program Analysis Data - East and Southeast Asia - DGM, PATHA, ANOVA - Aver. Correlation, ANOVA - Sq. Root of Aver. Correlation (Box 632)
    - Program Analysis Data - 20 Program Countries (Box 633)
    - Postpartum Program Files - Grants, 1
      - Follow-Up Survey - General (Box 636, Folder 11)
      - T70.74A/2 - Venezuela - MCP (Box 636, Folder 12)
      - T70.74A/3 - Venezuela - FPA (Box 636, Folder 13)
      - T70.74A/4 - Hong Kong (Box 637, Folder 1)
      - T70.74A/5 - Turkey (Box 637, Folder 2)
      - T70.74A/6 - Thailand (Box 637, Folder 3)
      - T70.74A/7 - Iran (Box 637, Folder 4)
      - T70.74A/8 - Philippines (Box 637, Folder 5)
      - T70.74A/9 - Colombia (Box 637, Folder 6)
      - T70.74A/10 - Djakarta (Box 637, Folder 7)
      - T70.067C - Mexico (Box 637, Folder 8)
      - Puerto Rico (Box 637, Folder 9)
      - Pakistan (Box 637, Folder 10)
      - csd-1565 - Reports (Box 637, Folder 11)
      - csd-1565 - Proposals, Contracts, Amendments (Box 637, Folder 12)
      - AID-csd-1565, 1966-1972 (Box 638, Folder 1-6)
      - AID/La-550 - Latin America (Box 638, Folder 7-10)
      - AID/NESA-391 - India, 1968-1972 (Box 639, Folder 1-11)
      - AID/NESA-391 - India, 1968-1972 (Box 640, Folder 1-8)
      - Africa - General (Box 641, Folder 1-2)
      - Nigeria (Box 641, Folder 3)
      - T72.0113C - Nigeria - Lagos Island (Box 641, Folder 4-5)
      - Iran (Box 641, Folder 6)
      - T72.16 and T72.16A - ME - Iran - Farah Maternity Hospital (Box 641, Folder 7-12)
      - T70.124 - Iran (Box 641, Folder 13)
      - Brazil (Box 642, Folder 1)
      - Ceylon (Box 642, Folder 2-4)
      - Colombia (Box 642, Folder 5)
      - Costa Rica (Box 642, Folder 6)
      - T69.062 - El Salvador (Box 642, Folder 7)
      - Honduras (Box 642, Folder 8)
      - T69.053 - Nepal (Box 642, Folder 9)
      - Taiwan - General Correspondence (Box 643, Folder 1)
      - T68.141 and D69.48 - Taiwan (Box 643, Folder 2)
      - D65.39, T67.127, D65.138 - Taiwan (Box 643, Folder 3)
      - T70.55 - IPPF and Ford, 1970 (Box 643, Folder 4)
      - IPPF (VFPA), 1969-1971 (Box 643, Folder 5-7)
      - T70.159 - Latin America - Colombia (Box 643, Folder 8)
      - AID Correspondence, 1965-1975 (Box 643, Folder 9-13)
      - AID csd-2155 (Box 644, Folder 1-2)
      - AID Expanded Postpartum Program - Africa (Box 644, Folder 3)
      - AID Expanded Postpartum Program - Asia (Box 644, Folder 4)
      - AID Expanded Postpartum Program - Latin America (Box 644, Folder 5)
      - AID Expanded Postpartum Program - General (Box 644, Folder 6)
      - Postpartum Program Progress Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 644, Folder 7)
      - Postpartum Program Progress Reports and Final Report, 1970-1974 (Box 645, Folder 1-5)
      - Colombia (Box 646, Folder 1-2)
      - Honduras (Box 646, Folder 3-9)
      - Mexico (Box 646, Folder 10-17)
      - Mexico (Box 647, Folder 1-19)
      - Venezuela (Box 648, Folder 1-8)
      - Brazil (Box 648, Folder 9-25)
      - Indonesia (Box 649, Folder 1-9)
      - Indonesia (Box 650, Folder 1-6)
      - Philippines (Box 650, Folder 7-19)
      - Philippines (Box 651, Folder 1-13)
      - Hong Kong (Box 651, Folder 14-18)
      - Hong Kong (Box 652, Folder 1-13)
      - Indonesia (Box 652, Folder 14-16)
      - Indonesia (Box 653, Folder 1-17)
      - Thailand (Box 654, Folder 1-21)
      - Thailand (Box 655, Folder 1-26)
      - Thailand (Box 656, Folder 1-35)
    - Srikantan, K. S. - Monograph Files and Drafts - "Social, Economic, Demographic, and Family Planning Factors Associated with Fertility Levels", 1975-1976 (Box 657, Folder 1-7)
    - Srikantan, K. S. - Monograph Files and Drafts - "Social, Economic, Demographic, and Family Planning Factors Associated with Fertility Levels", 1975-1976 (Box 658, Folder 1-5)
    - Srikantan, K. S. - Monograph Files, Drafts and Manuscript - "Social, Economic, Demographic, and Family Planning Factors Associated with Fertility Levels", 1975-1976 (Box 659, Folder 1-2)